BGM
Here we go, Apkami!
This time with us Yume Kudo of Juice=Juice
and Mei Yamazaki from Morning Musume。 24.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal of our
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
And now, this is the 400th time we've broadcasted "upkami"!
Yay!
Wow!
We'd like to share with you some of our favorite videos from the past editions.
I, Kudo, would like to start with my favorite video project from about 8 years ago.
Let's see...
I like to watch the recording of "Kipon Ascending" a lot.
The way to sing the A melody of "Key Pong Ascending" is very difficult.
The director said
The director said that it was very difficult to sing the A-melody of the song
But it's really hard to sing like that, so I try to sing the song from the recording video.
But it's really difficult, so I try to watch the recording video every time I sing.
Do you have any?
Yamazaki, I watched a video of Morning Musume・24's "Strongest Dance Lesson" recently.
It was very interesting. When the teacher was saying that they were going to stop, they all stopped, and the teacher went around like this with various people to check their moves,
I liked it when Mariya Makino and Reina Yokohama, who were at the very front of the group, looked at each other like this.
I like it because it's super funny.
It's super funny.
I watch it a lot.
The dawn of everyone is that it is the most interesting.
In the dance lesson, I'm going to say
I'm going to take a dance lesson with Ako Imigeta and Haruka Inoue.
and Haruka Inoue's voice training and dance lessons right after they joined the group.
I really like to watch the individual lessons of Ako Imigeta and Haruka Inoue.
It's a great value for money.
What?
You know...
Rehearsal footage of the senior members of the 25th anniversary concert will also be shown together.
So, please look forward to the future APU-KAMI broadcasts.
Let's start with this episode of Apkami!
Vocal Recording of Kanba Ishiguri, who breaks Chiba's "Ocha no oma".
First of all, let's start looking for her.
I'm sure even Mr. Mengers will be able to hear your baby voice singing.
I've been so busy with this for so long, I can't believe it's him.
The girl eventually learns to wear makeup and act with a slovenly face
After a time of being protected, she starts looking for a way to fight.
I know, but...
The baby voice...
Yes, sir!
I heard a lot of grunting
Yes, sir.
I heard you a lot.
The pattern of not suppressing the "ro" in "ro" and the "ka" in "naruka" and going strong
Even Mr. Menger echoed the song with his ubiquitous voice.
The "ro" was done in a mature way, but it was done in a powerful way.
Music
Even Mr. Mengers would have echoed the song with his baby voice.
When I bought the Rescence, I didn't know what I was getting myself into
And then the B melody
Yes, sir.
When you're broken, you start looking for a way to fight back.
You know, the victims of the Great Surgery Company and all that.
The world is a place where you know you're about to break yourself...
Possibility
The smoothness of the assailant and the assailant and the assailant and the assailant and the assailant.
the assailant and the assailant and the assailant
Yes, and, and, and... is it a little long?
Yes.
Victim, Purnova, and mostly assailant
The world's dying unreasonableness, break your own defeat, strike with your life.
A little more simple and longer with that hand
Yes, sir.
It's a big surgery company or something that comes
The inexhaustibility of a dying world. Strike with your life to defeat yourself.
Rust.
Yes, sir.
The world's unreasonableness that you see, strike with a life that breaks your fears.
There are so many possibilities, even if I'm dancing with someone else
I'm me, and I'm good at more than that
If common sense is being used, you should believe in yourself
Whether you cry or laugh today's the day
I've given up the lies, I've given up the beautiful dreams
Let's live free
You know, the drums, the accent changes like dada, it's totally done.
Yes, sir.
The normal part where it says there are so many possibilities...
Tintin...
I wanted more strength in the snare part.
I mean, more of a slow and steady...
A little more intensity.
Yes, yes...
I want to make the snare stronger.
Yes.
Then just believe in yourself.
Whether you cry or laugh
Today's the day anyway
A beautiful dream
Let go of the lies
Let's live free
All the beautiful dreams All the lies
It's a hamo, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
If I don't learn, I'll act like a clumsy bitch.
Start looking for a way to fight.
Oh, it's good.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, shit.
This is... uh...
Can you hear yourself while you do it?
Yes! I'll try. I don't know.
I might get hung up.
I'll start looking.
You got it.
It's perfect. - It's perfect.
Oh, my...
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much.
From the latest single from the tea ceremony.
You have seen the recording of Kanami Ishiguri's "Blood is Yaburu"!
Thank you very much.
I love the way your voice sounds from the very first shot, and the way your low voice sounds so cool.
I was thinking how nice it was, and at the same time, it made me nostalgic.
You're right, it was very Kanami-chan.
The way her eyes were downcast or the way she was concentrating.
It made me smile.
I thought it was really cool.
What did you think?
I used to do "MeeMee" like "MeeMee" when I was a trainee.
It brought back memories.
It was so cute how you turned into an impulsive thing when you saw it.
Kanami Ishigiri always remembers to keep the camera on her.
I think the recording session was filled with that kind of goodness.
The song "Konochi wa Yabeeru" is very impressive with Kanami standing there with her whole body in front of the camera.
I was so happy to see the recording today because I love this song as well as its power.
I was so happy to be able to see the recording of the song today.
I want to talk about it all the time, and I want to see it again.
I wanted to see the music video again, and I thought it looked really fun with all the weapons.
And when I was watching the music video
I was so happy to be able to tell Kanami directly that I really liked her here.
I'm going to watch a lot of music videos and I'm going to enjoy them a lot.
That's all for now.
Ocha no oma
Tea no oma
Chia Yaburu is now on sale!
Let's try to be cheerful!
Next up is here!
Morning Musume。24Songs for a somewhat sentimental occasion
Vocal recording by Miki Nonaka
Yes, please!
The night is deep, it's awfully heavy
After spending the night with you, my heart is falling
Just friends, but friends nonetheless
Two or three times and you'll only get tired
I bet you weren't like this before
I'm sure you weren't like this once, no matter who you were
I used to have a good time, just fine
I was the girl of your dreams, the girl of your dreams, the girl of your future
Those good old days when hard work brought results
The days when I felt like I could make anything come true
Peace of mind
Yes, healing
I'm not looking for anything extravagant, just keep it simple
The rhythm of this song is really detailed.
I had a lot of fun recording this song.
I had a lot of fun recording this song, feeling the rhythm and making sure to get the rhythm right.
I had a lot of fun recording it, feeling the rhythm and taking care of the nuances.
I had a lot of fun recording this song.
It's getting late at night, and it's getting awfully heavy.
Good night.
After spending the night with you, my heart is down.
Just friends, but friends nonetheless
I'm tired of going through two or three
I bet you weren't like this before
I'm sure you weren't like this once, no matter who you were
I used to have a good time
The A melody
I was directed to sing the A melody with a little bit of restraint.
Of course, the rhythm is finely tuned.
I had to be careful with that.
The point was to sing with a little bit of sentimentality.
There were some parts where the melody didn't have a melody to tell the story of a friend who is just a friend.
I tried to convey the nuance of the lyrics and the meaning of the lyrics in the song.
I tried my best to convey the nuance of the lyrics while putting them into the rhythm of the song.
When I watched the videos, I just watched them all.
It's just consuming my time.
I know I should just go to bed early
Love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love
the kindness of people, of people, of people
the older I get, the harder I find everything to be
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
love love love love love love love love
the depth of the love of the love of the love of the love of the love of the love of the love of the love of the love of the love
of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love of love
of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people
I find everything more difficult the older I get
And then there's the B melody
B melody has some difficult points.
Personally, I think this is the most difficult point.
The words "love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love
The melody goes "ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta".
The melody moves from one part to another in detail.
I think the most difficult point is to move the melody within this short section.
I think that's the most difficult point.
Yes, I thought so.
I thought so. I thought this was the most difficult point, because it was fast, you had to speak smoothly, and the melody changed.
Thank you for watching!
Don't say my lies
Everything inside me is transparent
When I was a little girl
As it is
The older I get, the more difficult I find it
All of my tears are transparent
not a single cloud, not a single pure imaite
And then the chorus... it's a bit of a pause, isn't it?
Not tears, tears, tears, but tears, tears.
That was a fun part for me.
It was very fresh for me to make a hesitation like that.
And the rhythm was fun too.
And the last part of the chorus...
The last part of the chorus is a little less orchestral.
The last part of the chorus is a little more relaxed than the previous choruses.
I really enjoyed the change of pace in the chorus.
Maybe "fun" is not the right word.
I thought it was fun to sing that part, too.
It was a very enjoyable recording.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
You have seen the video of vocal recording of Miki Nonaka, a song from Morning Musume。24's latest single, a song for a somewhat sentimental occasion.
Wow, that was amazing!
As Ms. Nonaka said, the rhythm of the song was very difficult and the pitch didn't rise and fall very much.
I also thought it was difficult when I was recording it, but Nonaka-san seemed to be having a lot of fun with it.
I also thought it was difficult for me to record it, but you were having a lot of fun recording it, and it was really wonderful.
I thought that Nonaka-san was singing "inside of me"...
Can't you hear it? I was just thinking that.
I'll be more conscious of it next time.
Listen to it.
I'm singing with a pinched inside.
You discovered that because Nonaka-san recorded it.
That's true.
My drive is...
I had to sing this A melody with very few notes.
Nonaka's hands were picking up the notes all the time.
I was first of all impressed by the way he was doing it.
I was also impressed that you were able to get to the point where you were able to enjoy recording this song.
I also thought it was really cool that you were able to put so much effort into the recording of this song.
If you were singing while reading the lyrics, you probably wouldn't be able to turn it around, so you really need to have the lyrics in mind.
I thought it's a song that you can't sing unless you have the lyrics in your head.
I thought it was really cool that you were able to sing without biting your tongue
I thought it was really cool to see you singing without biting your tongue.
Also, I can't stop!
I love the recoding gate.
I love the way your throat was open from the very first word.
I thought it was so nice that you could easily produce a high voice even though it wasn't so guttural.
I thought it was wonderful.
I really enjoyed listening to it.
That's all for Morning Musume。 24
A song for a sentimental moment
It was a vocal recording of Miki Nonaka.
How are you?
Thank you for your hard work.
Up-coming from Yume Kudo of Choo Choo's and Mei Yamazaki of Morning Musume。 24
Here is the next one!
Tsubaki Factory Seishun Exabyte
Vocal recording of YOHURUNO
This song is also a bit bouncy.
I think it would be easier to get more triplets
I think it would be easier to take the triplets.
I think it's easier to sing this song with that image.
It's easier to sing.
Two beats in a row.
Let's try it that way.
Yes, sir.
Love, dreams, friends... there's more than one thing that's important.
It's better to be reckless than to be right.
You can't carry it over.
Someday.
Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary
Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary
I can't carry it over.
I feel it.
Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary Momentary
Let's try one more time.
Music
Love, dreams, friends... there's more than one thing that's important.
It's better to be reckless than to be right.
I can't carry it over.
Someday it'll be good.
I'm sure it'll be good.
No surprises, please.
Okay, let's do it.
It's better to be reckless than to be right.
I can't carry it over.
And give me a promise of someday someday someday.
But, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'd rather see you now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh my god.
The first half of the song is about someday someday someday.
The second half of the song, I'm more than happy to meet you now, too.
Let's put both.
Give me a promise of someday someday but I'm happier with "I'll see you now
I yeah yeah yeah yeah mountain my life
Okay, B melody number one. Basically, the freshness remains the same, and after the latter half of the song, let's play a little bit of crescendo.
I'm more than happy to meet you now.
I yeah yeah yeah
Maintain my life Perfect diamonds, it doesn't matter if you're not good at it
I'm sorry for being so lazy and reckless.
I don't know, maybe it's a little short...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And, though Gamashira and Yakumo are low, keep up the good work.
Just a little bit of desperation and a little bit of darkness.
I'm sorry it's only Kamoshira and Yakumo, but I want to say Hajimeki, Hajimekitte, and I want to be greedy!
I want to be greedy, I want to be greedy, I want to be greedy
I want to be greedy
Okay, I'll get the rhythm out there.
I'll get the rhythm out there.
I'll see you now, I'm more happy to see you in the world
Yeah Yeah Yeah
I want to be a diamond in the rough, I want to be a diamond in the rough, I want to be a diamond in the rough
I'm sorry I'm only doing this in the dark clouds, I want to be greedy
OK, then, let's try the chorus
Gansha Yakumo Dake Dake Dake Yakumo Dake Hachikutte Dake Hachikutte Dake Hachikutte Dake Hachikutte Dake
Touch it, touch it, touch it, touch it Yellow Bomman
I want to show you, I want to show you, I want to show you, I want to show you
I want to show you, I want to show you, I want to show you
vivid DPI
now, with fleta fleta fleta fleta fleta fleta
I want to show you I want to show you I want to show you I want to show you I want to show you
You don't have to do it so hard.
You don't have to do it that strongly.
Fleta fleta fleta fleta fleta
It should all sound like "freta".
Just leave a little E at the end.
Fleta Fleta Fleta Fleta Thai
Enable mumber
You don't want to show too much.
So you want to touch it?
I don't think you should want to touch it.
I don't think that would be good for the flow.
It's not like you have to choose. It's nonsense. I'll leave it to you.
I want to show, I want to show, I want to show.
Vivid DPI.
Yeah, it's good.
Okay, bye.
Bloomin' Bloomin'
I want to show, I want to show, I want to show.
Vibrant DPI
Bloomin' Bloomin' Bloomin' smiles
Bloomin' Bloomin' tears
Always full of eyes
Bloomin' Bloomin' smile
Bloomin' Bloomin' tears
I'll burn it in my heart
Bloomin' Bloomin' Bloomin' Tears
It's a triplet right there
I'll keep all of them there.
That's what I'm talking about.
Broomin' deben't give up
Broomin' value
Misses are a must.
Yes, it was perfect. Then we're done for today!
Yay! Thank you for your hard work!
You have seen the vocal recordings of Youth EXAVITE and YOFURU NO from SUNOKI FACTORY's latest single!
Thank you very much. I didn't think I would be able to see the recording video of RUNO-chan, so I was very happy,
I was so happy to see the video, but I couldn't help but feel like she was singing with a lot of energy.
I was very happy to see the recording video of RUNO-chan, as I never thought I would be able to see it... I felt that the way she sings with her power removed and the groove of RUNO-chan in this recording was very nice.
I also thought her singing voice was really good. I really like Runo's singing. I thought it was very pleasant, with a lightness and a penetrating feeling. How did you like it?
When the director said, "Let's do this rhythm here," you could sing it immediately, and I could tell that you were singing with that in mind.
It was fun to listen to the rhythm of the song.
I would like to see more RUNO-chan performances.
This was the vocal recording of Tsubaki Factory's Youth EXA Bite, YOFU RUNO.
Tsubaki Factory New Single "Seishun Exabite
Now on sale
Let's take it easy today.
It's time to say goodbye to Yume Kudo and Mei Yamazaki of upcami!
We've seen a lot of footage from the recording sessions. It was very interesting.
I, Yamazaki, listened to Miki Nonaka's recording of a sentimental song, which made me want to listen to the recordings of all the other Morning members.
The director told me that the phrases at the beginning of the first song are totally different from one person to another, so I really wanted to listen to different people's recordings.
I was also very happy to be able to watch Kaname Ishiguri's recording with Mei Yamazaki, who is also a member of the group.
I was also very happy to be able to watch Kaname Ishiguri's recording video with my colleague, Mei Yamazaki, but I was also looking forward to seeing her in her casual clothes.
I was thinking, "Kaname-chan, you've got an empty space here," or "You're wearing your hair like this today...
I love Kaname-chan, so I was very happy to be able to take a good look at her and listen to her singing, which was really fun.
I could feel from the way she sang that she loves to sing and record vocals.
I think it's wonderful that you enjoy singing on the recordings, and it's also great that you are so sincere about it.
I also think it's really cool that you are so sincere in your singing.
I'd like to keep an eye on her from now on.
In Apkami, you can get a behind-the-scenes look at the production process of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We'll introduce you to the parts you don't usually get to see, so please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time on Apkami
I'll be talking with Yume Kudo of JuiceJuice and
and Mei Yamazaki from Morning Musume。 24.
Good bye.
Next time on Upokami, we'll have a makeup lecture by that member from JuiceJuice
And Tsubaki Hattori, we will show you the recording of Baby Spider!
Enjoy!
Thank you for watching!